<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<plugins>
    <plugin>
        <name>Cage</name>
        <handle>cage</handle>
        <short-description>Craft Age-Verification Plugin</short-description>
        <link-store>https://plugins.craftcms.com/cage</link-store>
        <price>19 $</price>
        <description><![CDATA[
            This plugin provides a simple way to add an age-verification-gate to your website, where the user has to verify their age.<br>
            It allows site administrators to have age-restricted sections on the website, where only adults can enter.<br>
            All this happens on a nice looking page which you can customize <b>a lot</b>! (You can even have some custom CSS)<br>
            <br>
            The plugin also features a lot of different ways the user can verify their age:<br>
            Drop-Downs? Input Fields? Just some buttons? This plugin has everything.<br>
            <br>
            If you have adult-content, or content that is not intended to be seen by minors, this is probably the best and only plugin on the market right now!<br>
        ]]></description>
        <link-github>https://github.com/SkayoCrafts/cage</link-github>
        <link-packagist>https://packagist.org/packages/skayocrafts/cage</link-packagist>
        <docs>https://github.com/SkayoCrafts/Cage/blob/master/DOCS.md</docs>
    </plugin>

    <plugin>
        <name>Sidebar Shortcuts</name>
        <handle>sidebar-shortcuts</handle>
        <short-description>Add Shortcuts to the CP Sidebar</short-description>
        <link-store>https://plugins.craftcms.com/sidebar-shortcuts</link-store>
        <price>Free</price>
        <description><![CDATA[
            This plugin adds the functionality to add simple shortcut-links to the sidebar in the control panel of Craft CMS.<br>
            This is useful for quick access to various plugins or other important stuff!<br>
            For example if you have a a settings page from plugin that you visit often, like "cage/settings/appearance", you can add a Shortcut to the sidebar and get there with just one simple click, instead of three!<br>
            <br>
            I originally made this plugin just for myself, as a little time-saver, but I found it so useful that I wanted to share it!
        ]]></description>
        <link-github>https://github.com/SkayoCrafts/Sidebar-Shortcuts</link-github>
        <link-packagist>https://packagist.org/packages/skayocrafts/sidebar-shortcuts</link-packagist>
        <docs>https://github.com/SkayoCrafts/Sidebar-Shortcuts/blob/master/DOCS.md</docs>
    </plugin>

    <plugin>
        <name>Social GitLab</name>
        <handle>social-gitlab</handle>
        <short-description>GitLab integration for Social</short-description>
        <link-store>https://plugins.craftcms.com/social-gitlab</link-store>
        <price>Free</price>
        <description><![CDATA[
            This plugin provides a <a href="https://gitlab.com" target="_blank">GitLab</a> integration for
            <a href="https://github.com/dukt/social" target="_blank">Social 2 for Craft CMS</a>,
            so you can add OAuth2 authentication via GitLab to your Craft CMS Site!
        ]]></description>
        <link-github>https://github.com/SkayoCrafts/social-gitlab</link-github>
        <link-packagist>https://packagist.org/packages/skayocrafts/social-gitlab</link-packagist>
        <docs>https://github.com/SkayoCrafts/social-gitlab/blob/master/README.md</docs>
    </plugin>
</plugins>